<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Travel on Roger Counihan Blog</title>
    <link>https://www.rogercounihan.com/categories/travel/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Travel on Roger Counihan Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.rogercounihan.com/categories/travel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Jackson Hole Photography &amp; Snowboarding</title>
      <link>https://www.rogercounihan.com/posts/travel/jackson/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.rogercounihan.com/posts/travel/jackson/</guid>
      <description>Introduction After complaining enough about not getting a quick west coast ski trip in, Melissa offered to let me take a few days to myself in Jackson Hole prior to meeting the family in Steamboat for our winter family trip.
Arrival &amp;amp; Scouting I arrived at Jackson Hole airport around midday, and after somehow losing my luggage at the worlds smallest airport, jumped in the rental car and started exploring. Driving north into Grand Teton National Park, I scoped out Glacier View, Snake River View, and a couple other turnouts from the road.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coyote Gulch 3 Day Backpack</title>
      <link>https://www.rogercounihan.com/posts/travel/coyotegulch/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.rogercounihan.com/posts/travel/coyotegulch/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In October 2018, my brother and I did a quick three day hike in Coyote Gulch, within the Grand Staircase National Monument, outside Escalante, UT. Julian’s son’s due date was November 28th, so we were barely getting this trip in.
Our initial target was Zion NP, but based on concerns about crowding, and the trans-Zion trek being significantly impacted because of access limitations in the northwest corner of the park, we honed in on Grand Staircase outside of Escalante.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
